seymourduncan.com 2018-10-19

# Privacy Policy - Seymour Duncan | Seymour Duncan

All of us at Seymour Duncan really do care about protecting your privacy and personal information. We certainly don’t like getting spammy emails ourselves or when companies sell our personal information. The following privacy policy goes over the information you share on this website and what we do with it. As always, if you have any questions feel free to ask us.

By using this website you may get a cookie (not the delicious kind that can be found at the Seymour Duncan Factory, but the kind that helps us know what you have in your cart) in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first visit our website. / By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

  2. **Collecting personal information**

         We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information in order to fulfil orders, improve the user experience and for marketing purposes. Including: Information derived from IP address, information you provide when registering for the forum or to order something on this website (including email address, name, address and date of birth, card details), information that you post on the forum for publication on the internet and any other personal information you choose to provide.

  3. **Using your personal information**

Personal information submitted to us through our website will be used for the purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the website. Please note, your personal information will be never be sold or rented to a company not owned or directly answerable to Seymour Duncan.

We will use it to personalize the website for you, as well as the marketing (online ads, etc). It will be used to send goods you may have purchased online (some of that information, including your email address and shipping address may be shared with a 3rd party dealer who (local music store) who will fulfil your order. Seymour Duncan uses several 3rd party ad and Analytics services that may collect information such as browser cookie ID, URL visited, device ID and other provided information. We might occasionally send you an email about our products but don’t worry, we won’t do so very often and you can easily unsubscribe at any time.

Keep in mind that all information posted on the forum is public, otherwise the information you provide to the forum, and birthdays are public while your email is kept private to only Seymour Duncan and the volunteer moderation team. We may occasionally send you an update on the latest happenings at Seymour Duncan.

         All pickup and pedal purchases are handled through a 3rd party called Shopatron. You can review the provider’s privacy policy at http://ecommerce.shopatron.com/privacy-policy. We will share information with our payment services provider only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. Shopatron has several layers of security to ensure that your billing details are kept encrypted and secure.

  4. **Disclosing personal information**

We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy. Basically anyone who needs to know in order to help you out and only that information which is required for the task at hand.

         We may disclose your personal information to any member or group of companies related or owned by Seymour Duncan. We may also disclose it if the police show up and tell us that we have to disclose such information or otherwise required to do so by law. However, if requested by your spouse as to whether you just purchased a new Les Paul, we will maintain absolute secrecy.

  5. **Security of your personal information**

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall-protected) servers. All billing data will be sent over encrypted SSL.

You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping the password you use for accessing our website confidential; we will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to our website).

  6. **Updating the Privacy Policy**

We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy.

  7. **Your rights**

If you have any questions about any information we hold, want something updated, deleted or amended – please let us know and we are happy to oblige. You can unsubscribe from product news communications at any time.

  8. **Third party websites**

         Our website includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party websites (including Jazz and heavy metal fan sites). We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies and practices of third parties.

  9. **Updating information**

         Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

  10. **Cookies**

         Our website uses cookies.

         A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This is how we know you are the same session as opposed to a different computer every time you navigate to a different part of the website.

         Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

         We use both session and persistent cookies on our website. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies in order to further provide a better personalized experience and more appropriate recommendations.

The names of the cookies that we use on our website, and the purposes for which they are used, are set out below:

(a)     we use both session and persistent cookies on our website to recognise a computer when a user visits the website / track users as they navigate the website / enable the use of a shopping cart on the website / improve the website’s usability / analyze the use of the website / administer the website / prevent fraud and improve the security of the website / personalise the website for each user.

Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites. If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website but will still be able to browse the website.

  11. **Our details**

         This website is owned and operated by Carter Duncan Corporation.

         We are registered in California and our office is at 5427 Hollister Ave, Santa Barbara, California.

You can contact us by writing to the business address given above or by using our website contact form or by using the contact us form.
